Expose the corruption. Protect the hive.
The Beekeeper is a action, crime, thriller film directed by David Ayer.
One man's campaign for vengeance takes on national stakes after he is revealed to be a
former operative of a powerful and clandestine organization known as Beekeepers.
Adam Clay, played by Jason Statham.
Agent Verona Parker, played by Emmy Raver-Lampman.
Derek Danforth, played by Josh Hutcherson.
Wallace Westwyld, played by Jeremy Irons.
Agent Matt Wiley, played by Bobby Naderi.
Mickey Garnett, played by David Witts.
The Beekeeper is a 2024 action thriller film produced and
directed by David Ayer and written by Kurt Wimmer.
It stars Jason Statham, Emmy Raver-Lampman, Josh Hutcherson, Bobby
Naderi, Minnie Driver, Phylicia Rashad, and Jeremy Irons.
The film follows a retired government assassin who sets out for revenge after
his kind-hearted landlady falls victim to a phishing scam.
The Beekeeper was released in the United States by Amazon MGM Studios and
in the United Kingdom by Sky Cinema on January 12, 2024.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed
$162.6 million worldwide against a budget of $40 million.
A sequel, The Beekeeper 2, is scheduled for a
theatrical release on January 15, 2027.
The film explores themes of massachusetts, secret government
organization, frantic, vengeance, fbi agent.
The tone is intense.